{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Swimming Pool Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40123/":{"taskOID":40123,"originalTaskOID":40123,"setID":434,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":7579,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of pool is in need of repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11513,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11514,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7580,"questionDisplayText":"Pool Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What primary material is the pool surface made of?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11515,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11516,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11517,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11518,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11519,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7581,"questionDisplayText":"Repair Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the repair needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11520,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl lining repair","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl lining repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11521,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pool cover needs repair","answerDisplayText":"Pool cover needs repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11522,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Filtration system not working","answerDisplayText":"Filtration system not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11523,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pool surface is cracked or flaking","answerDisplayText":"Pool surface is cracked or flaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11524,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tile needs repair","answerDisplayText":"Tile needs repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11525,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want to replace or add accessories","answerDisplayText":"Want to replace or add accessories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11526,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Heater not working","answerDisplayText":"Heater not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11527,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11528,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want to remove/fill in pool","answerDisplayText":"Want to remove/fill in pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":7579,"questionDisplayText":"Type of Pool","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of pool is in need of repair?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":11513,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11514,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11513,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Above ground","answerDisplayText":"Above ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11514,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"In ground","answerDisplayText":"In ground","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7580,"questionDisplayText":"Pool Material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What primary material is the pool surface made of?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11515,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11516,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11517,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11518,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11519,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11515,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11516,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Concrete","answerDisplayText":"Concrete","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11517,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Tile","answerDisplayText":"Tile","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11518,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Unsure","answerDisplayText":"Unsure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11519,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Fiberglass","answerDisplayText":"Fiberglass","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7581,"questionDisplayText":"Repair Description","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What best describes the repair needed?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11520,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl lining repair","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl lining repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11521,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pool cover needs repair","answerDisplayText":"Pool cover needs repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11522,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Filtration system not working","answerDisplayText":"Filtration system not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11523,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pool surface is cracked or flaking","answerDisplayText":"Pool surface is cracked or flaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11524,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tile needs repair","answerDisplayText":"Tile needs repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11525,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want to replace or add accessories","answerDisplayText":"Want to replace or add accessories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11526,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Heater not working","answerDisplayText":"Heater not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11527,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11528,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want to remove/fill in pool","answerDisplayText":"Want to remove/fill in pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11520,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Vinyl lining repair","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl lining repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11521,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Pool cover needs repair","answerDisplayText":"Pool cover needs repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11522,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Filtration system not working","answerDisplayText":"Filtration system not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11523,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Pool surface is cracked or flaking","answerDisplayText":"Pool surface is cracked or flaking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11524,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Tile needs repair","answerDisplayText":"Tile needs repair","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11525,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Want to replace or add accessories","answerDisplayText":"Want to replace or add accessories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11526,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Heater not working","answerDisplayText":"Heater not working","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11527,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11528,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want to remove/fill in pool","answerDisplayText":"Want to remove/fill in pool","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":13,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40123/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40123,"taskName":"Swimming Pool or Accessories - Repair or Service","taskDescription":"Repair or Service Swimming Pool or Accessories","xmTaskDescriptor":"Swimming Pool Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":1204,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Pool Swimming ground renovation plaster","textMessagingName":"Svc Pool","rolloverLongDesc":"Often done by the same contractors who handle pool maintenance.","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes cracks, leaks, pipes, etc.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Service Swimming Pool or Accessories.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Swimming Pool Repair Service \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Pool Leak Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":61,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Swimming Pool Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Swimming Pool or Accessories - Repair or Service","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Swimming Pool Project","urlName":"Swimming-Pool-or-Accessories-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Pool Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Pool Leak Repair","searchKeywords":"Pool,Swimming,ground,renovation,plaster,material,landscaping,maintain,filter,remodeling,costs,vinyl,servicies,sauna,replacement,heater,redo,care,maintenance,tub,hot,glass,fiber,concrete,cement,above,inground","emcCategoryOid":-12070,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":434,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}